Mars 2020 Perserverance
Lands on Mars!
We are starting the
Straighten Up and
Fly Right maneuver
in preparation for
parachute deploy
[Music]
[Whoosh. Click.]
The navigator has confirmed that the parachute has deployed
and we are seeing
significant deceleration.
[Music]
[Click
Wind whooshing]
Skycrane maneuver
has started.
[Rockets roar]
About 20 meters
off the surface.
[Control voice unintelligible]
[Rockets roar]
Touchdown confirmed!
Perseverance safely
on the surface of Mars
ready to begin seeking
signs of past life@
Looks like we're getting
the first image.
[Applause continues]
This is the most amazing thing!
This is what NASA does.
This is what we can do
as a country.
[Music]